A Guide to the Cary Young Adams Papers, 1988-2006
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Cary Young Adams Papers, 1988-2006
The Library of Virginia
43040
23.7 cubic feet (53 boxes)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Cary Young Adams, Norfolk.
Biographical Information
Cary Perkins Wynne Young was born in Norfolk, Virginia on 12 February 1927. She is the daughter of John Hughes Young (1881-1949) and Mary Curtis Wynne (1888-1974). She married Donald C. Adams (1926-2010) on 29 January 1983.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1988-2006, of Cary Young Adams (b. 1927) of Norfolk, Virginia, containing genealogical research files on the Cary, Chisman, Curtis, Harwood, Hill, Hubbard, Hughes, Jones, Lee, Mallicote, Moss, Perkins, Whitaker, Wills, Wynne, and Young families. Adams' research interests were on these families who settled in Charles City, Dinwiddie, Elizabeth City, Gloucester, Isle of Wight, James City, Nansemond, Norfolk, Southampton, Warwick, and York Counties, Virginia, and North Carolina and England. The collection contains Bible records, book catalogs, brochures, guides, and indexes to records in various institutions, census records, citations, queries, and surname exchange information from various genealogical websites, clippings, correspondence, genealogical charts, genealogical and hereditary society applications and other materials, maps, military and pension records, newsletters, obituaries, passenger lists, photographs, published sources, tax records, tombstone inscriptions, and vital statistics.
Contents List
- Books, Films, CD's - Lists. (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
- British Isles Vital Records Index, Second Edition: England, Ireland, Scotland, and Wales FamilySearch Family History Resource File (16 compact discs). (Box 53)
- Cary - Associatied Families. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Cary - Charts and Books. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Cary - Miscellaneous. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Cary - Obituaries and Cemeteries. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Cary - Other Branches. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Cary - Vital Records. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Cary - Wills and Court Records. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Cemeteries. (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
- Census Records. (Box 1, Folder 13-15)
- Charts. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Charts - Forms. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Chisman. (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
- Cincinnati, Society of the. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- City Directories. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Civil War. (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
- CW Library. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Computer. (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence - Boelt, Frederick. (Box 2, Folder 12-14)
- Correspondence - Bowman/Graybeal. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Correspondence - Ellis. (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
- Correspondence - Frayser. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - Hansford. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Correspondence - Johnson. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Correspondence - Rogers. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Correspondence - von Schilling. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Correspondence - Woodward. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Correspondence - Miscellaneous - Incoming. (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Correspondence - Miscellaneous - Outgoing. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Council Journals. (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Curtis. (Box 3, Folder 13-15)
- Curtis - Associated Families. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Curtis - Bible, Wills, Cemetery, Ohits, Vital Records. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Curtis - Cary - Whitaker - Prentis. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Curtis - Court Records. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Curtis (Early). (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Curtis - England. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Curtis - Land Records. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Curtis - Minson. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Curtis - Miscellaneous. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Curtis - Moreland - Hansford. (Box 4, Folder 10-12)
- Curtis Notebook. (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Curtis - Pictures. (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Curtis - Tabb - Purefoy. (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
- Curtis - Unfiled. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Curtis - Wade. (Box 5, Folder 4-6)
- D.A.R. Library. (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Deep Creek Farm - Aerial Photo. (Box 5, Folder 8)
- DNA. (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Draft - Book. (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Elizabeth City County. (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Elizabeth City County - Tax and Census. (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
- Emigrants (Patents). (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Emigration - Passengers and Ships. (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
- English Parish Records: Gloucestershire, Wiltshire, Berkshire, Oxford, Worcestershire Ancestry.com (compact disc). (Box 53)
- English Parish Records: Hampshire, Kent, Surrey Sussex Ancestry.com (compact disc). (Box 53)
- English Parish Records: London Ancestry.com (compact disc). (Box 53)
- Forms. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Fort Eustis. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Guide to Research Materials in the North Carolina State Archives - Section B: County Records. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Handwriting, etc.. (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
- Harwood. (Box 6, Folder 11-12)
- Harwood. (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
- Harwood - Articles. (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
- Harwood - Charts. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Harwood - Charts (Map-case 2, Drawer 12)
- Harwood - "Endview". (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Harwood - Hereward Records and Papers. (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Harwood - Military. (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Harwood - Miscellaneous. (Box 7, Folder 10-11)
- Harwood - Other Counties. (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Harwood - "Water View". (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Hereditary Societies. (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Hill -Wynne. (Box 8, Folder 4-8)
- History - Peninsula. (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Houses. (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Hubbard. (Box 8, Folder 11-12)
- Hubbard. (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
- Hughes - Associated Families. (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Hughes - Charts. (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Hughes - Emigration. (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Hughes - Gloucester County. (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Hughes - James City and York Counties. (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
- Hughes - Miscellaneous Counties. (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
- Hughes - Norfolk County. (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Hughes - Tax and Census. (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Hughes - Warwick County. (Box 9, Folder 13-14)
- Isle of Wight. (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
- Isle of Wight Order Book, 1746-1752. (Box 10, Folder 3)
- James City County. (Box 10, Folder 4-6)
- James City County - Tax and Census. (Box 10, Folder 7-8)
- James City County - Will Witnessed by Col. Richard Lee (compact disc), ca. 1650. (Box 53)
- Jamestowne Society. (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Jones. (Box 10, Folder 10-11)
- Jones. (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
- Jones - Associated Families. (Box 11, Folder 3-5)
- Jones - Bolling Batte Papers. (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Jones - Bible Records. (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Jones - Charts. (Box 11, Folder 8-10)
- Jones - Charts (Backup). (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Jones - Charts (Final). (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Jones - Court Records. (Box 11, Folder 13-14)
- Jones - Early Records. (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Jones - England. (Box 12, Folder 2)
- (Matthew) Jones House. (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
- Jones House Association News. (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
- Jones - Isle of Wight. (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Jones - North Carolina. (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Jones - Obituaries. (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Jones - Other Counties. (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Jones - Pictures. (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Jones - Servant. (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Jones - Southampton County. (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Jones - Southampton County - Marriages. (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Jones - Southampton County - Wills/Deaths. (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Jones - Tax and Census. (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
- Jones - Tyler's Quarterly, etc.. (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Jones - Vital Records. (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Jones - Warwick County - Miscellaneous. (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Jones - Warwick County - Wills. (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Jones - Wood. (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
- Kirn Library. (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
- Land Platting. (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Land Records. (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Lee - Associated Families. (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
- Lee, Baker/Wills Lee Line. (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Lee - Bible Records. (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Lee - Census Records. (Box 14, Folder 6-8)
- Lee - Charts. (Box 14, Folder 9-11)
- Lee - Charts. (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Lee - Charts (Wills Lee Line) (Map-case 2, Drawer 12)
- Lee - Court Records - 1600's. (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
- Lee - Court Records - 1700's. (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
- Lee - Court Records - 1800's. (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Lee - Davis. (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Lee - DNA. (Box 15, Folder 8-9)
- Lee - Early. (Box 15, Folder 10-11)
- Lee - Elizabeth City County. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Lee - England. (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
- Lee - Gloucester County. (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Lee - Goochland County. (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Lee - Goodwin. (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
- Lee Hall. (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
- Lee Hall - Photographs. (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Lee - Haynes. (Box 16, Folder 10-12)
- Lee, Henry/Whitaker Lee Line. (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Lee - James City County. (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Lee - Kiskyacke. (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Lee - Marrow. (Box 17, Folder 3-5)
- Lee - Miscellaneous. (Box 17, Folder 6-8)
- Lee - Nansemond County. (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Lee - Northern Virginia. (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Lee - Obituaries. (Box 17, Folder 11-12)
- Lee - Other Counties. (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Lee - Pictures. (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Lee - Presson. (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
- Lee, Richard - Accomack and Northampton Counties. (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Lee, Richard - Article. (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
- Lee, Richard - Books, Articles. (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Lee, Richard - England. (Box 18, Folder 8-9)
- Lee, Richard - Norfolk County. (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Lee, Richard - Shropshire/Worcester. (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Lee, Richard - Signatures. (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Lee, Richard (William Thorndale). (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Lee, Richard - York County. (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
- Lee, Richard Cary. (Box 19, Folder 3)
- The Lees of 17th Century York County, Virginia by Catherine H.C. Seaman. (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Lee - Sclater. (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Lee - Tax Records - Warwick County. (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Lee - Tax Records - York County. (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Lee - Tyler's, etc.. (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Lee - Unfiled. (Box 19, Folder 9-10)
- Lee - Vital Records - Births. (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Lee - Vital Records - Marriages. (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Lee - Vital Records - Deaths. (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Lee - Warwick County. (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Lee, William/Henry Lee/John R. Lee Line. (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Lee, William H./William Lee/Aspen Line. (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Lee - York County. (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Lee - York County - Tax Records. (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Leigh. (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Library of Congress. (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Library of Virginia. (Box 20, Folder 8-10)
- Mallicote. (Box 20, Folder 11-12)
- Mallicote. (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
- Mallicote - Dunn. (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
- Maps - Local. (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Maps - Migration. (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Maps - Virginia. (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Marriage Index: Selected Counties of KY, NC, TN, VA, WV, 1728-1850 Family Tree Maker's Family Archives (compact disc). (Box 53)
- Martiau. (Box 21, Folder 8)
- McIntosh - Young. (Box 21, Folder 9-10)
- Miles. (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Military Records - Colonial/Indian Wars. (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Archives. (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Cary. (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - D.A.R.. (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Guides. (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Harwood. (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Hughes. (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Jones, Abridgton. (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Jones, John (Warwick County). (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Kirby, John. (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Lee, Francis. (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Lee, John. (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Lee, William. (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - LVA Research. (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Miscellaneous. (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Moss, John. (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Navy. (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Newman, Thomas. (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Pension/Bounty Land. (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Registers. (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Whitaker, William et al.. (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Wills, Matthew. (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Wynne. (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Military Records - Revolutionary War - Young. (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Military Records - War of 1812. (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Military Records - Mexican War. (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Military Records - Confederate - Davis. (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Military Records - Confederate - Green. (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Military Records - Confederate - Jones, Andrew J.. (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Military Records - Confederate - Jones, Duroc H.. (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Military Records - Confederate - Jones, Henry F.. (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Military Records - Confederate - Lee, Baker P.. (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Military Records - Confederate - Lee, Edward T.. (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Military Records - Confederate - Lee, Frank. (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Military Records - Confederate - Lee, Wills. (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Military Records - Confederate - Mallicote. (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Military Records - Confederate - Marrow. (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Military Records - Confederate - Newman, Thomas. (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Military Records - Confederate - Research. (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Military Records - Confederate - Whitaker, George W.. (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Military Records - Confederate - Whitaker, Richard C.. (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Military Records - Confederate - Whitaker, Richard H.. (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Military Records - Confederate - Wynne. (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Military Records - Confederate - Young, John H.. (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Military Records - Confederate - Young, Washington W.. (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Military Records - Confederate - Young, William G.. (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Military Records - Confederate - Young, William Lee. (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Military Records - World War I. (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous - Genealogy. (Box 24, Folder 13-15)
- Moore. (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Moss. (Box 24, Folder 17-18)
- Moss - Court Records. (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Moss - Court Records. (Box 25, Folder 1-3)
- Moss - Thelma Hansford Compilation. (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Moss - Vital Records. (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Museums. (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Nansemond County. (Box 25, Folder 7)
- National Archives. (Box 25, Folder 8)
- National Burial Index for England & Wales, Second Edition Federation of Family History Societies (4 compact discs). (Box 53)
- National Genealogical Society. (Box 25, Folder 9-11)
- Newman. (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Norfolk County. (Box 25, Folder 13-15)
- Norfolk Public Library. (Box 26, Folder 1)
- North Carolina Genealogical Society. (Box 26, Folder 2)
- North Carolina - Maps. (Box 26, Folder 3)
- North Carolina Research. (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Pending. (Box 26, Folder 5-6)
- Perkins. (Box 26, Folder 7-10)
- Perkins - Associated Families. (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Perkins - Baker. (Box 26, Folder 12-13)
- Perkins - Charles City and Henrico Counties. (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Perkins - Charts and Notes. (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Perkins - Court Records. (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Perkins - Dinwiddie County. (Box 27, Folder 2-3)
- Perkins - Early. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Perkins - England. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Perkins - Norfolk. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Perkins - Other Areas. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Perkins - Vital Records, Obituaries, Cemeteries. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- PERSI - Periodical Source Index. (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Photographs. (Box 27, Folder 10-13)
- Piersey - Hill. (Box 27, Folder 14-15)
- Queries and Name Exchanges. (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
- Research. (Box 28, Folder 3-6)
- Research - Articles, Books. (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Research - Courthouses - Notes. (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Research - England. (Box 28, Folder 9-13)
- Research - England - Books. (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Research - England - Cambridgeshire Family History Society. (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Research - England - London. (Box 29, Folder 3-5)
- Research - England - Societies. (Box 29, Folder 6-8)
- Research - LDS. (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Research - Libraries - Notes. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Research - Notes. (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Researchers. (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
- Rockefeller Library - Colonial Williamsburg. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Scasbrooke. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Seminars. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Swem Library. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Swem's Index. (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Tidewater Genealogical Society. (Box 30, Folder 8)
- To Be Mailed. (Box 30, Folder 9)
- University of Virginia. (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Virginia Beach Genealogical Society. (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Virginia Beach Library. (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Virginia - Colonial Records. (Box 30, Folder 13-15)
- Virginia - Colonial Records. (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Virginia Colonial Records Project. (Box 31, Folder 2-5)
- Virginia Colonial Records Project - Pending. (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Virginia Colonial Records Project - Young - Pending. (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Virginia County Records. (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Virginia Court Records - Wills. (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Virginia Gazette. (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Virginia Genealogical Society. (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Virginia Historical Society. (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Virginia History. (Box 32, Folder 2-3)
- Virginia Newspapers. (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Virginia Tax Records. (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Virginia Vital Records. (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Virginia War Museum. (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Warwick County. (Box 32, Folder 8-10)
- Warwick County - Census and Vital Records. (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Warwick County - Court Records. (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
- Warwick County Minute Book, 1748-1762. (Box 33, Folder 4-6)
- Warwick County - Tax Records. (Box 33, Folder 7-9)
- Whitaker. (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
- Whitaker, Alexander. (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Whitaker - Associated Families. (Box 34, Folder 4-6)
- Whitaker - Barbados. (Box 34, Folder 7-8)
- Whitaker - Bible Records. (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Whitaker - Books. (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Whitaker - Census and Tax Records. (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Whitaker - Charts. (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Whitaker - Chicheley/Chesley. (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Whitaker - Collier. (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Whitaker - Computer. (Box 35, Folder 3-6)
- Whitaker - Court Records - 1600's. (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Whitaker - Court Records - 1700's. (Box 35, Folder 8-9)
- Whitaker - Court Records - 1800's. (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Whitaker - Early Records. (Box 35, Folder 11-12)
- Whitaker - Early Records. (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
- Whitaker - Early Records. (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
- Whitaker - Early Records - Patents. (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Whitaker - Elizabeth City. (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Whitaker - Elizabeth City - Tax and Census Records. (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Whitaker - Emigration. (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Whitaker - England. (Box 36, Folder 7-10)
- Whitaker - England - Cambridge. (Box 36, Folder 11-14)
- Whitaker - England - Cambridge - Associated Families. (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
- Whitaker - England - Cambridge - Associated Families - Bourchier. (Box 37, Folder 3-4)
- Whitaker - England - Cambridge/Lancashire - Books. (Box 37, Folder 5-6)
- Whitaker - England - Cambridge - Charts. (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Whitaker - England - Court Records. (Box 37, Folder 8-9)
- Whitaker - England - Lancashire. (Box 37, Folder 10-11)
- Whitaker - England - LDS Research. (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Whitaker - England - London. (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Whitaker - England - Research Correspondence. (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
- Whitaker - Gouge/Gough. (Box 38, Folder 3-5)
- Whitaker, Jabez. (Box 38, Folder 6-9)
- Whitaker - James City County. (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Whitaker - Lineage. (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Whitaker - Maryland Historical Society. (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Whitaker - Military Records. (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Whitaker - Miscellaneous. (Box 39, Folder 3-5)
- Whitaker - North Carolina. (Box 39, Folder 6-7)
- Whitaker - Pictures. (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Whitaker - Richmond. (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Whitaker - Sandefur. (Box 39, Folder 10-11)
- Whitaker - Tax and Census. (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Whitaker - Unfiled. (Box 39, Folder 13-14)
- Whitaker - Vital Records - Births. (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Whitaker - Vital Records - Marriages. (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Whitaker - Vital Records - Deaths. (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Whitaker - Walker. (Box 40, Folder 4-6)
- Whitaker - War of 1812. (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Whitaker - Warwick County. (Box 40, Folder 8-9)
- Whitaker - York County. (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Whitaker - York County Project (CW). (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Wills Family. (Box 40, Folder 12-13)
- Wills Family. (Box 41, Folder 1-4)
- Wills Family - Associated Families. (Box 41, Folder 5-7)
- Wills Family - Court Records. (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Wills Family (Fred Eggleston). (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Wills Family - Fred Eggleston Files. (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Wills Family - Filmer. (Box 41, Folder 11-12)
- Wills Family - Montgomery Files. (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Works Progress Administration. (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Wynne. (Box 42, Folder 4-7)
- Wynne - Associated Families. (Box 42, Folder 8-9)
- Wynne - Bible Records. (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Wynne - Census Records. (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Wynne - Charts. (Box 42, Folder 12-13)
- Wynne - Civil War Letters (Typed Transcriptions). (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Wynne - Court Records - 1600's to 1700's. (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
- Wynne - Court Records - 1800's. (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Wynne - Early Records - 1900's. (Box 43, Folder 4-7)
- Wynne, Elizabeth Maxwell Alsop - Journals (Typed Extracts). (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Wynne - Emigration. (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Wynne - England. (Box 43, Folder 10-12)
- Wynne - England - Bedford. (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Wynne, Francis Edmund, Sr. - Memoirs. (Box 44, Folder 2-3)
- Wynne - Miscellaneous. (Box 44, Folder 4-7)
- Wynne News. (Box 44, Folder 8-10)
- Wynne - Obituaries. (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Wynne - Other Areas. (Box 45, Folder 2-3)
- Wynne - Pictures. (Box 45, Folder 4-5)
- Wynne - Research by F.E. Wynne. (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Wynne - Reunion. (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Wynne - Tax Records and Census. (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Wynne - Vital Records - Births. (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Wynne - Vital Records - Marriages. (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Wynne - Vital Records - Deaths. (Box 45, Folder 11)
- York County. (Box 46, Folder 1-4)
- York County - Census. (Box 46, Folder 5)
- York County - County Officers and Vital Records. (Box 46, Folder 6)
- York County - Hansford Charts. (Box 46, Folder 7)
- York County - Maps (1704 Rent Roll Holdings) (Map-case 2, Drawer 12)
- York County - Tax Records. (Box 46, Folder 8-9)
- York County Project - Charts. (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Young - Accomack and Northampton Counties. (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Young - Arms. (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Young - Associated Families. (Box 47, Folder 3-5)
- Young - Bible Records. (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Young - Books, Magazines, etc.. (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Young - Census. (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Young - Charts. (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Young - Charts - Branches. (Box 47, Folder 10-11)
- Young - Charts - Samuel. (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Young - College Records. (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Young - Cook. (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Young - Correspondence. (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Young - Court Records - 1600's-1700's. (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Young - Court Records - 1800's. (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Young - Crandol. (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Young - Denbigh. (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Young - Early Virginia - Emigration and Patents. (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Young - Elizabeth City County. (Box 48, Folder 7-8)
- Young - England. (Box 48, Folder 9-11)
- Young - Garrow. (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Young - Gloucester County. (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Young - Isle of Wight County. (Box 49, Folder 1-3)
- Young - James City County. (Box 49, Folder 4-6)
- Young - Miscellaneous. (Box 49, Folder 7-8)
- Young - Miscellaneous Virginia Counties. (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Young - Newspaper Articles. (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Young - Norfolk - 1600's. (Box 50, Folder 1)